非常好，做完这些让我们看看
All right, you're done. Lets look at the
解决方案。现在需要开始在抽象线程的
solution. We'll begin by adding a log tag
SyncAdapter代码中加入一个LOG_TAG常量。既然这个抽象线程是在
into our abstract threaded SyncAdapter. Since this stuff
后台运行的，因此产生程序运行日志信息是非常有帮助的。
runs in the background, it's really helpful to have
我们最终还是希望能够在用户没有察觉的情况下
some logging. Since we ultimately want to run
运行SyncAdapter所要完成的任务。让我们把位置请求代码从
the SyncAdapter in undetected mode. Let's pull the location
utility 类里拿出来。然后我们把这些代码
query from our utility class. And then we
粘贴到已经建立的sunshine 服务中。
paste in the code from our existing sunshine service.
下面必须要补充一些东西。我们需要调用getContext方法来获取
We'll have to patch a few things up. We'll have to call getContext to
当前的内容， 举例来说。 请注意，我在复制主要的方法的同时我也
get the current context, for example. Note that I copied over ad location at
复制了地点的数据。最后，
the same time I copied over the primary function. And then finally, we'll fix
我们来使用一个新的helper函数来完成我们的
update weather to use the new helper
SyncAdapter。 让我们来运行一下。
function in our SyncAdapter. Let's run this.